The fateful entanglements of two men in love with the same woman.
Hanover Street is a drama, romance, war film directed by Peter Hyams.
Margaret is a nurse in England during WW2, and married to a secret agent.
Things get complicated when she falls for David, an American pilot.
David Halloran, played by Harrison Ford.
Margaret Sellinger, played by Lesley-Anne Down.
Paul Sellinger, played by Christopher Plummer.
Maj. Trumbo, played by Alec McCowen.
Harry Pike, played by Max Wall.
Sarah Sellinger, played by Patsy Kensit.
Hanover Street is a 1979 romantic war film written and directed by Peter Hyams, and
starring Harrison Ford, Lesley-Anne Down and Christopher Plummer.
The film explores themes of london, england, secret
mission, world war ii, bomber pilot.
The tone is emotional.